{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1949",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2004.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1949",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 April 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2004.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 5 March 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 28 May 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 5 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 5 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 1 January 1999.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2014,",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 1 January 1999.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022,",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022,",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2014,",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 April 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 24 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2004.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "7 March 2024",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "7 March 2024",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "7 March 2024",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "7 March 2024",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 4
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1994",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1994",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2024",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2023",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1949",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1949",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1949",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2020.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 1949.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2009.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 1949.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 28 May 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2009-03-26.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2009-03-07.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 1 April 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2023",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 2, 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2024",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 1949.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 1949.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
      "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ]
}